Zachary Wilson

253 Fairystone Ln, Lexington, NC 27295 (336) 813-6925 | <u>zachmwilson33@yahoo.com</u> Make new email- gmail

CAREER SUMMARY

Accomplished professional with experience in customer-facing demands, construction assistance, restaurant support, and team leadership. Proven track record in excellent customer service, successful new employee training, and exceeding performance objectives. Excellent communicator accustomed to working under pressure and prioritizing multiple tasks to ensure client satisfaction.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CHARTWELLS - Prep/Breakfast Chef; Greensboro, NC August 2018 - Present

• Ensure that the food prep area and kitchen are well maintained throughout the shift • Restock the kitchen for subsequent shifts • Properly store food items in locations with the appropriate temperature • Prepare omelet dishes that have been submitted by students and faculty • Keep the trayline fully stocked

RUBY TUESDAY - Chef/Dishwasher/Expo/Salad Bar Attendant; Thomasville, NC July 2017 - May 2018

• Collaborate with the head of kitchen and cooks to prepare meals during dining hours • Properly store food items at appropriate temperatures • Restock kitchen for subsequent shifts • Ensure that the food prep area and kitchen are cleaned and sanitized at the end of your shift • Clean and soak all dishes using appropriate equipment and deliver them to the appropriate area • Send food to tables in a timely manner while keeping quality in check • Maintain a clean and well-stocked garden bar throughout the shift

WILSON CONSTRUCTION – Construction Aide; King, NC June 2014 - August 2017

• Experience Includes- Installing windows, building decks, greenhouse assembly, remodels, renovations • Carry materials and supplies from trucks to job site so they are ready for installation or other tasks • Test equipment and machinery to ensure it is in good working order • Clean up job site at end of day and ensure all equipment is properly secure for the night • Learn carpentry, electrical work, plumbing and other specialized skills as required by the head contractor • Follow instructions to ensure safety of entire team • Measure and cut lumber to desired specifications

OUTBACK STEAKHOUSE - Backline/Frontline Assistant; Boone, NC February 2016 - July 2016

• Prepare food for subsequent shifts before opening • Maintain a clean and organized dish pit • Mop Front of House and ensure that the guest bathrooms are well-stocked and clean • Cook and prepare meals throughout the shift in a fast-pace work environment while maintaining quality

EDUCATION

Appalachian State University – General Studies August 2014 – May 2016 North Davidson High School – GPA: 3.92 (Cum Laude) June 2014 Coder Foundry – August 2018 – Present

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Rescue House Church – Grades K-2 Leader **Northwest Elementary School** – Special Events Volunteer